Hello everyone!
Hej allihopa!
Today we are going to talk about verbs.
Idag ska vi prata om verb.
is
sitter
located
ligger
hanging
hänger
one should - this table
ett borde - det här bordet
a cup
en kopp
a cup of tea
en kopp te
a water bottle
en vattenflaska
cactus
en kaktus
small cactus
en liten kaktus
red scissors
en röd sax
book
en bok
an interesting book
en intressant bok
banana
bananer
yellow bananas
gula bananer
It is a cup of tea on the table.
Det står en kopp te på bordet.
There is a water bottle on the table.
Det står en vattenflaska på bordet.
There is a small cactus on the table.
Det står en liten kaktus på bordet.
lies
ligger
There is a red scissors on the table.
Det ligger en röd sax på bordet.
There is an interesting book on the table.
Det ligger en intressant bok på bordet.
There are yellow bananas on the table.
Det ligger gula bananer på bordet.
a sofa
en soffa
There's a boy sitting on the couch.
Det sitter en pojke i soffan.
a chair
en stol
A girl is sitting on the chair drinking water.
Det sitter en flicka på stolen och dricker vatten.
one lamp
en lampa
three lamps
tre lampor
There are three lamps hanging from the ceiling.
Det hänger tre lampor i taket.
a pillow
en kudde
three pillows
tre kuddar
There are three pillows on the sofa.
Det ligger tre kuddar på soffan.
a painting
en tavla
There are two paintings on the wall.
Det sitter två tavlor på väggen.
a mirror
en spegel
There is a mirror on the wall.
Det sitter en spegel på väggen.
There is a mirror hanging on the wall.
Det hänger en spegel på väggen.
a clock
en klocka
There is a clock on the wall.
Det sitter en klocka på väggen.
Look!
Titta!
Now it's evening.
Nu är det kväll.
It's dark outside.
Det är mörkt ute.
Did you like the video?
Tyckte du om videon?
Did you not like the video?
Tyckte du inte om videon?
I enjoy.
Jag tycker om.
I do not like.
Jag tycker inte om.
Subscribe to my channel!
Prenumerera på min kanal!
Thanks for today!
Tack för idag!
Farewell!
Ha det så bra!